[
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"\"Entre nous\" means __________.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Between ourselves"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"\"faux pas\" means ___________.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Mistake"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"An adjective meaning 'pertaining to the sun.'", "answer":0, "answers":["Solar"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"From what Irish words is 'Dublin' derived?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dubh linn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"From what language is the term 'finito'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Italian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"From which language does the term 'Mayday' come?", "answer":0, "answers":["French"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"How do you say \"I Love You\" in German?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Ich liebe Dich"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Many Meanings:  Fuel, vapor, flattulence, helium.  What is it?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Many Meanings: Fuel, vapor, flattulence, helium. What is it", "answer":0, "answers":["Gas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Mardi Gras is French for ___________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Fat tuesday"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Merging the words 'melt' and 'weld' created which word?", "answer":0, "answers":["Meld"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Multiple Meanings:  Drinking utensils or sight-enhancers.", "answer":0, "answers":["Glasses"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Multiple Meanings:  Slamming your hands together quickly, or a venereal disease.", "answer":0, "answers":["Clap"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Name the soda that is often confused with a drug.", "answer":0, "answers":["Coke"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Other than Germany, whose official language is German?", "answer":0, "answers":["Austria"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Subject, verb and object are parts of a _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Sentence"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"The name Australia is derived from the Latin word \"australis\" which means _______.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Southern"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"The name for this semi_precious stone comes from the Latin for \"sea water\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Aquamarine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"The name for this semi-precious stone comes from the Latin for \"sea water\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Aquamarine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"The Scots call it 'shinty' - what do Canadians and Americans call it?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"The word rodent comes from the italian 'rodere', which means?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gnaw"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"This animal is found at the beginning of an (English) encyclopedia", "answer":0, "answers":["Aardvark"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What city's name is derived from the words 'dubh linn'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dublin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What do the initials 'VCR' stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Video Cassette Recorder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does 'A&W' (of root beer fame) stand for ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Allen & Wright"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does 'alma mater' mean in English?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bountiful mother"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does 'AOL' stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["America Online"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does 'majuba' mean?", "answer":0, "answers":["Place of rock pigeons"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does 'shogun' mean in English?", "answer":0, "answers":["Military governor"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does \"c'est la vie\" mean?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["That's life"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does \"c'est la vie\" mean\"", "answer":0, "answers":["That's life"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does N.A.S.A stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["National Aeronautics and Space Administration"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does S.O.S. stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Save Our Souls"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does SOS stand for", "answer":0, "answers":["Save Our Souls"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does the abbreviation N/A mean?", "answer":0, "answers":["Not applicable"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does the acronym 'scuba' mean?", "answer":0, "answers":["Self Contained Underwater Breathing Apparatus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does the Greek root word 'chrom' mean?", "answer":0, "answers":["Color"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does the Irish 'dubh linn' mean?", "answer":0, "answers":["Black pool"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What does the word 'karate' translate to in English?", "answer":0, "answers":["Open hand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is 'blackpool' in Irish?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dubh linn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is 'bountiful mother' in Latin?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alma mater"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is 'military governor' in Japanese?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shogun"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the English word for 'fiesta'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Festival"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the first letter in the Greek alphabet?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alpha"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the Israeli 'knesset'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Parliament"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the language of Hungary?", "answer":0, "answers":["Magyar"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the last letter in the Greek alphabet?", "answer":0, "answers":["Omega"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the literal meaning of 'pince-nez'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pinch nose"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the meaning of the Mercedes Benz motto 'Das beste oder nichts'?", "answer":0, "answers":["The best or nothing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the official language of Austria?", "answer":0, "answers":["German"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the official language of Senegal?", "answer":0, "answers":["French"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the Old English word for 'sneeze'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fneasan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the only English word formed by the first three letters of the alphabet", "answer":0, "answers":["Cab"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the only English word formed by the first three letters of the alphabet?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cab"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What is the Spanish word for 'festival'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fiesta"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What ONE word fits ____hood; ____hole; ____date.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Man"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What ONE word fits ____stream; ____hill; _____pour.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Down"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What ONE word fits? ____hood; ____hole; ____date.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Man"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What ONE word fits? ____stream; ____hill; _____pour.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Down"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What three letter word means the same as \"to ingest\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eat"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What three letter word means the same as \"to ingest\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Eat"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What two words make the word 'meld'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Melt and weld"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What was the language of ancient India?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sanskrit"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What word contains the combination of letters: \"xop\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["SaXOPhone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"What word contains the combination of letters: \"xop\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Saxophone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Which is the only english word that contains all the vowels in alphabetical order?", "answer":0, "answers":["Facetious"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Which two fruits are an anagram of each other?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lemon and melon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"LANGUAGE", "lang":"en", "tags":["LANGUAGE"], "question":"Which word means \"profound boredom\" in both french and english?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Ennui"], "source":""}
]
